{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which is of the following not correct rule for writting variables names.","correct_answer":"spaces are allowed while naming these.","incorrect_answers":["These need to be in the lowercase or camel case","These could be mix of letters, Numbers, _ or $","you cannot start with a number"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Variable is not case sensitive","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"One of the follwing statements is correct","correct_answer":"var myVariable = 'Hello'","incorrect_answers":["var myVariable = /Hello/","var myVariable = 'Hello'","var myVariable = Hello"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"which the camel case variable name is correct","correct_answer":"var myCodeDate = 'c'","incorrect_answers":["var my _code_date = 'c'","var MycodeDate = 'c'","var MyCodeDate = 'c'"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which of the following operator is used for the Assignment Operator?","correct_answer":"=","incorrect_answers":["!","==","+"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"4 types of variables are:","correct_answer":"Boolean, String, int, double","incorrect_answers":["Boolean , String, Variable, conditions","Boolean , String, Numbers, loops","Boolean , String, ints, while loops"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Variables are useful because they allow us because:","correct_answer":"store data and change the results of a program.","incorrect_answers":["they store data and delete the programs","change the results of a program only and does not store data"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"A variable is like a container with a name that can hold a value.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Kyle is writing a program. He wants to use a variable that can store the money information. The money will have decimal points so he can display exact change. Which variable he needs to use.","correct_answer":"Float","incorrect_answers":["String","Boolean","Integer"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Madison is creating a JavaScript program. She likes to add some information that must print as is. She knows that she will need "" around her data but what type of variable she is using.","correct_answer":"String","incorrect_answers":["Boolean","Ints","Float"]}]}
